SEAN MILFORT

System Administrator II

seanmilfort@me.com

Harrisburg, PA

 \bowtie

seanmilfort.com

linkedin.com/in/seanmilfort in

blog.seanmilfort.com @SeanMilfort

@SeanMilfort

@SeanMilfort

Summary

System Administrator II with 6+ years of experience implementing new solutions and strategies in multiple organizations. Passion for development work and learning different languages for building side projects during free time. Currently working on a master's degree for Computer Information Science.

Work Experience

Rite Aid | Camp Hill, PA

System Administrator II

September 2021 - Present September 2021 - Present

- Maintaining AirWatch MDM Environment for 10,000+ devices
- Developing/Testing New Technologies for Store Environment

WellSpan Health | York, PA

System Administrator

December 2019 - September 2021

December 2019 - September 2021

- Creating/Developing Application Packages & Software Installations for mass/minor deployments
- Creating Technical/Support Documentation for new & existing solutions
- Evaluating/Designing Technical Solutions to improve End User Workflow
- Developing/Troubleshooting Mobile Device Management Solutions (AirWatch)
- Maintaining/Improving IT Environment with new Technological Improvements

Burlington Stores, Inc. | Burlington, NJ

April 2015 – November 2019

IT Integration Analyst II

November 2017 - November 2019

- Responsible for large-scale Engineering/Design changes to our Mobile Device Management Platform (AirWatch) containing 11,000+ devices (iOS, Android & Windows CE)
- Created Installer/Scripting Packages for silent installations for 15,000 Machine (Unix Scripting, PowerShell & Bash)
- Developed/Maintained the Base Computer Image for 4,000+ machines (Windows/Mac)
- Created/Edited/Deployed Group Policy 15,000+ active devices
- Evaluated/Met with Senior Business Partners/Vendors on multiple different initiatives

IT Integration Analyst I

April 2017 - November 2017

- Implemented/Led Microsoft Surface Project in Corporate/Field Environment
- Planned/Integrated New Technology into Current Environment
- Maintained/Deployed Bi-Quarterly Updates to 4,000+ Machines
- Handled Maintenance/Support/Upgrades of Mobile Device Management Product (AirWatch) containing 11,000+ active devices
- Researched/Suggested Solutions to improve Productivity/Performance

IT Integration Associate

October 2016 - April 2017

- Helped Create/Set the company standard for Corporate Level Devices (Windows/Mac)
- Created Mobile profiles and packages for iOS Devices in Corporate/Store Environment for 4,000+ Mobile Devices
- Authored/Maintained Support and Procedural Documentation for Support Teams
- Created/Deployed Software Packages on large scale for Endpoints (Windows/Mac)

Client Technologies Technician I

April 2015 – October 2016

- Supported/Troubleshooted Windows and Mac Machines on a large scale
- Participated in many different with various projects with different departments in IT
- Supported Mobile Devices (iPad and iPhones) while utilizing AirWatch as MDM tool
- Basic Network troubleshooting and configuration (DNS, VLAN, Connectivity)
- Delivered Customer Service to Troubleshoot and Enhance End User Experience

Skills

Languages
JavaScript
HTML & CSS
PowerShell

Bash Scripting

OS Management (Windows, macOS, Android, Linux & iOS) Mobile Device Management Active Directory & Group Policy Management

Infrastructure Skills

Large Scale Packaging & Deployment Microsoft Deployment Toolkit **Interpersonal Skills**

Leadership
Teamwork
Technical Documentation
Customer Service
Communication

Awards

CIO Award

Dennis Hodgson, CIO, Burlington Stores, Inc. *April 2018*

CEO Award

Thomas Kingsbury, CEO, Burlington Stores, Inc. *September 2017*

Education

La Salle University, May 2022

Master of Science (M.S.), Computer Information Science

Philadelphia, PA

La Salle University, May 2015

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Computer Science

Philadelphia, PA